[Music]
[Música]
very good What's up family How are you paying
muy buena Qué pasa familia Cómo estáis
attention to this news that could
atentos a esta noticia que puede
change everything and the truth is It could
cambiarlo todo y que la verdad Nos puede
give us a drastic ending that in the end is not what we
dar un drástico final que al final no
expected The truth is that
sea el que esperamos la verdad es que
I am very disappointed to have
estoy muy decepcionado de haberme
woken up today with this news and I hope
despertado hoy con esta noticia y espero
that the reason is very very important I am not going
que el motivo sea muy muy de peso no voy
to play or comment
a jugar ni voy a opinar tampoco en plan
against the lawyer or anything like that
en contra del abogado o algo por el
without knowing what the reasons are
estilo sin saber cuáles son los motivos
then in a little while I will be able to get
luego dentro de un ratillo podré ponerme
in touch with people around me and with people who
en contacto con gente del entorno y con
know the case and who are
gente que conoce el caso y que está
involved and also people who have contact
metida y además gente que tiene contacto
with Carlota and so on so that they can inform me
con Carlota y demás para que me informen
and let me know what has happened
y me hagan saber qué es lo que ha pasado
here What are the reasons and what is
aquí Cuáles son los motivos y qué es lo
so important that
que tiene tanto peso como para que el
Carlota Prado's lawyer resigned
abogado de Carlota Prado haya renunciado
days before because this trial
días antes servicio porque este juicio
was scheduled for the 3rd and the
estaba programado para el día 3 y el día
8th or in other words next week suddenly
8 o sea la semana que viene de repente
with all the years that we have been
con todos los años que llevamos
waiting for justice to be done for this
esperando que se haga Justicia con esta
girl the lawyer
chica el abogado
Santiago Marín who you already know was
Santiago Marín que ya sabéis que estuvo
on Antonio David's Channel giving
en el Canal de Antonio David dando
explanations how he wanted to handle the case
explicaciones cómo quería llevar el caso
from more to resigned
de más a renunciado
we put the worst family we put the worst
metemos lo peor familia metemos lo peor
before continuing with the video as
antes de continuar con el vídeo como
always remind you to
siempre recordaros que le deis a
subscribe okay it's completely
suscribir vale que es completamente
free to give the video a like and
gratuito que le deis like al vídeo y
above all tell me what you think is
sobre todo que me digáis que pensáis que
going to happen with this and what you think about
va a pasar con esto y qué opináis de que
the lawyer
el abogado
resigning at the last minute to see the
renuncie en el último momento a ver el
trial it can be paralyzed it can be
juicio se puede paralizar se puede
paralyzed it can be suspended okay if they don't
paralizar se puede suspender vale si no
reach an agreement in which they choose
llegan a un acuerdo en el que elijan
lawyers or what or he chooses a
abogados o que o que escoja uno de
public defender as far as I know it can be suspended
oficio que yo sepa se puede suspender
again and it can be postponed again and
otra vez y se puede aplazar otra vez y
all this issue
todo el tema este
and this would already be desperate okay I don't
y esto ya sería desesperante vale No
want to play lawyer I don't want to give a
quiero jugar al abogado no quiero opinar
negative opinion until I know
en plan negativo hasta que no sepa
what the reasons were for why he
Cuáles han sido los motivos por el que
decided to
ha decidido
give up this case you know and we saw it
desistir este caso ya sabéis y lo vimos
when Antonio had interviewed this
cuando Antonio había entrevistó a este
lawyer on his channel that this lawyer
abogado en su canal que este abogado
wanted to give the case a twist and he would have
quería darle una vuelta al caso y le
liked it to be restarted
hubiera gustado como que se reiniciara
like taking a step back because it turns out
como dar Un paso atrás porque Resulta
that he
ser que
was being tried for
que se estaba juzgando por abusos
sexual abuse not as if it were
sexuales no como si fueran abusos
sexual abuse without penetration and this lawyer
sexuales sin penetración y este abogado
I wanted another crime to be played, not that it is with penetration And then the sentences and the convictions would take something much bigger that was a completely impossible thing Okay, any jurist and any lawyer and any judge will tell you, you cannot go back in
va a decir no se puede volver atrás en
a process,
un proceso
judicial processes have a
los procesos judiciales tienen un
procedural system that is immovable It's
sistema procesal que es inamovible Es
like when you have a
como cuando tú tienes una audiencia
preliminary hearing and you deliver the evidence and then
previa y entregas las pruebas y luego de
suddenly they find more evidence it's no
repente encuentran más pruebas no te
good to you, I mean, if you haven't presented it yet,
vale o sea si no las has presentado ya
even before the trial date, you can't
aunque sea antes de la fecha del juicio
present it anymore This is how it is
ya no puedes presentarlo Esto es así
okay, the procedural law has forms and you
vale la ley procesal tiene una formas y
have to follow them, but man, at
hay que seguirlas no pero hombre por lo
least in this trial, at least in
menos que este juicio por lo menos en
this trial where the prosecutor
que este juicio en donde el fiscal
requested a sentence, well, requested and
solicitaba una pena bueno solicitaba y
requests because at the moment
solicita porque esto de momento hasta
until the moment in which I am
hasta el momento en el que estoy
recording This video is still standing okay, the
grabando Este vídeo sigue en pie vale el
prosecutor needs a sentence for the accused
fiscal se necesita para el acusado una
of two years and six months in prison
pena de dos años y seis meses de cárcel
and compensation of 6,000 euros for both
y una indemnización de 6.000 euros tanto
José María Este and the
al tal José María Este como a la
production company, Zeppelin is
productora a Zeppelin
not going to jail, that is already
no va a entrar en la cárcel eso ya lo
clear okay because we are
tenemos claro vale porque estamos
talking about the sentence  maximum would be
hablando de que la pena máxima Serían
two years and six months the prosecutor
dos años y seis meses la fiscal
normally according to the experience I
normalmente según la experiencia que
have reading cases always asks for the
tengo leyendo caso siempre pide como lo
maximum but then it always stays at
máximo pero luego siempre se queda en
less okay so if the boy has no
menos vale entonces si el chico no tiene
criminal record or anything then it's almost certain
antecedentes ni nada pues es casi seguro
let's tell you almost 100% that this
vamos os digo casi al 100% que este
boy is not going to jail okay if they
chico a la cárcel no va a ir vale si le
sentence him to a year and a half to two years or
condenan a un año y medio a dos años o
whatever the boy is not going to jail he has to serve
lo que sea el chico a la cárcel no va
two years behaving well
tiene que estar dos años portándose bien
two years and I don't know how long it would not be to
dos años y no sé cuánto tiempo no sería
serve the two imagine if you sentence him to
cumplir los dos imagínate le condenas a
one year no then after a year he has to
un año no pues a partir del año tiene
wait another two and then the statute of limitations expires
que esperar otros dos y ya le prescribe
and he is totally clean as if
y queda totalmente limpio como si no
nothing had happened okay but he wo
hubiera pasado nada vale pero la cárcel
n't step foot in jail and 6,000 euros well they'll
no la pisa y 6.000 euros pues ya me
tell me no that it's 6000 euros for how bad
dirán no que son 6000 euros para lo mal
this girl is going through that you already
que lo está pasando esta chica que ya
know that well she is in that she is
sabéis que bueno que se encuentra en que
not in a state Well since
no se encuentra en un estado Bueno desde
this Big Brother thing happened and all that,
que pasó esto de gran hermano y demás
the girl well the videos the
pues la chica bueno los vídeos los
audios and everything that we've heard from
audios y demás que hemos escuchado de
her well they leave us with a very
ella pues nos dejan muy mal saber muy
bad taste in our mouths and the people who
mal sabor de boca y a la gente que le
love her and so on  Well, she's very
quiere y demás pues la tiene muy
worried, she's got people very
preocupada le tiene a la gente muy
worried, and man, this has to be
preocupada y hombre esto tiene que ser
an outrage and a tremendous disappointment
una indignación y una decepción tremenda
for the people who support her, for the people
para la gente que la apoya para la gente
who wear clothes, and for the people who look after
que la ropa y para la gente que vela por
her. I'm telling you now that I'm leaving
ella ya os digo yo ahora que salgo
because I have to go get the children and I
porque tengo que ir a por los niños y
have some meetings today regarding,
tengo hoy unas reuniones en referente a
well, I don't have the explanation either. Let's
bueno no tengo la explicación tampoco A
see, it's something private, okay. But it's something
ver es algo privado vale Pero es algo
family and so on, I have to go
familiar y demás tengo que tengo que
out and I'll be out all afternoon. I've already
salir y estaré toda la tarde fuera ya os
told you that there's no live today because I'm
he dicho que hoy no hay directo porque
not going to get there in time to be here
no voy a llegar a tiempo para estar aquí
at 8 with a live prepared and
a las 8 con un directo preparado
started and so on, okay. I recommend that you keep an
iniciado y demás vale Yo recomiendo que
eye on Albert Albert who
estéis pendiente de Albert Albert que ha
posted a tweet I just spoke with
puesto un tweet Acabo de hablar con el
Carlota Prado's lawyer who left
abogado de Carlota Prado que ha dejado
the defense of the former Big Brother in
la defensa de la ex gran hermano en el
this afternoon's live. I'm giving you the little bit I
directo de esta tarde os avanzo lo poco
can because it's a delicate case,
que puedo porque es un caso delicado
okay. Albert says he's going to say something, I'll
vale Albert dice que va a contar algo ya
tell you later I'll also have
os digo yo luego también tendré
information and I'll tell you, I'll probably
información y os la contaré seguramente
make another video where I'll update this
haré otro vídeo donde actualizaré esta
information from today. I was also watching
información de hoy estuve viendo también
the video in which my dear spoke. Speaking
el vídeo que habló mi querido Hablando
clearly, okay. But well, it's known.  little is
claro vale Pero bueno se sabe poco se
known and the little that is known, well,
sabe poquillo y lo poquillo que se sabe
as they could say Albert, it is not
pues como podrían dice Albert tampoco
possible to say. I don't know, I don't want to
que se pueda contar No sé no quiero
think that it is, I don't
pensar que sea
want to be suspicious, you know, I can't
no quiero ser mal pensado sabes que no
think of many reasons why
se me ocurren muchos motivos por los que
a lawyer could exist in the case, because he
un abogado pueda existir del caso porque
stopped believing in the victim, because he no longer
deje de creer en la víctima porque ya no
wants to support her, because this case is not
quiere apoyarla porque este caso no les
profitable for them, no, because we are
reporte ganancias no porque estamos
talking about a criminal case in which the
hablando de un caso penal en el que el
lawyer here, well, I don't know if he's going to get paid, because
abogado aquí pues no sé si va a cobrar
Carlota, I understand that, I don't know, I don't
porque Carlota entiendo que no no sé no
know if she's paying or what it's worth, because
sé si estará pagando o qué vale porque
the girl is how she is, I don't know the truth,
la chica está como está no sé la verdad
honestly, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to wait,
sinceramente voy a voy a Voy a esperarme
because right now I'm
Porque ahora mismo Me he quedado
blocked and I don't know, I can't think of
bloqueado y no sé no se me ocurren
many more reasons why the
muchos más motivos por los que el
lawyer could suddenly reject
abogado pueda rechazar ahora de repente
the case, or in other words, going back was
el caso o sea lo de Volver atrás era
impossible, but well, at least
imposible pero bueno por lo menos en
based on this, having tried to get the
base a esto haber intentado sacar lo
most out of it, I hope that at least the
máximo Yo espero que por lo menos la
compensation of 6,000 euros is
indemnización de 6.000 euros sí que sea
viable, both for José María and for
viable tanto la de José María como la de
the producer, that they have to
la productora que tengan que pedir
apologize, that the producer comes out, apologizes
perdón que salga la productora pedir
or something, please, and well, the two
perdón o algo por favor y bueno los dos
years and six months in prison, which
años y seis meses de cárcel que
surely weren't going to be two  years and
seguramente no iban a ser dos años y
six months okay because also the said
seis meses vale porque también el tal
José María Well, he will have his defense No, it's not
José María Pues tendrá su defensa No no
that they were a couple, it's not that they were already
es que eran pareja no es que ya se
sleeping together whatever okay anyway
acostaban lo que sea vale en fin
we'll see what happened
ya veremos a ver qué es lo que ha pasado
we'll see if they have a logical excuse
vamos a ver si tienen una excusa lógica
and well sincerely as always
y bueno sinceramente como siempre
I wish Carlota the best there are
desearle lo mejor a Carlota hay
colleagues who well she had said that I don't
compañeros que bueno había dicho que no
know that the case is not paralyzed, the case
sé que no se paraliza el caso del caso
if it continues I think so let's see
si sigue adelante yo creo que sí a ver
that it can continue because if things go
que puede seguir adelante porque a unas
badly she takes a public defender but if
malas ella coja uno de oficio pero si se
the trial can also be suspended or so that
puede suspender también el juicio o sea
can also happen maybe
eso también puede pasar puede que llegue
the day will come they don't come to an agreement no, it's not
el día no se pongan de acuerdo no no
the thing Clara and says well
esté la cosa Clara y diga pues se
the trial is suspended again and again
suspende otra vez el juicio y otra vez
postponed until next year through
aplazado hasta el año que viene a través
all of them you know when no and the fact
de todas saber cuándo no y el hecho de
that she takes a public defender well it's
que coja un abogado de oficio pues es
like for me I see the public defender
como por yo el abogado de oficio lo veo
as the helmet so that you don't get fined
como como el casco para que no te multen
no Or rather the public defender is not
no O sea el abogado oficio ni está
aware of the subject nor has he been one nor has he been
entera del tema ni lleva un ni lleva un
soaked in the subject for a long time and he's
montón de tiempo empapado en el tema y
not going to watch the same  For the client, he's not going
no va a velar igual por el cliente no va
to watch anyway, okay,
a velar igual vale
anyway, his family is from the session, what
en fin su familia es de sesión qué de
session are we going to see then I'll tell you something,
sesión vamos a ver luego cuento algo
okay, a hug and until the next
vale un abrazo y hasta el siguiente
video
vídeo
[Music]
[Música]